[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "Say we do all survive two years of campaign help, where does that leave our family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PDT", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "Hopefully, in the White House.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "That must make you feel great, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "I actually didn't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "It -- was that deliberate in your -- back of your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "You know, I think if it had been Hillary's story, I probably wouldn't have done it, as much as I admire her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "Why is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Well, that's one of the things our series is trying to find out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Do you feel like the whole barrier to the concept of a female president may change very quickly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Well, I suppose it could, but you sound more optimistic than I feel.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Do you remember that period at all, his political life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "What did that do to your view of politics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "EAVER: My father told us a wonderful story.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Was your father quietly smug when Nixon came crashing down, that his instinct about him had been proven right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Oh, no, I think he was heartbroken for the country.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nixon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RP", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Where do we look?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "You look up there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "I mean, do you feel more empathy with the pressures that go with that kind of job?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "That's an interesting question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "How do you -- how do you think President Obama's done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Well, I think -- I thought it was very interesting last week that he said he's really concentrated on policy, because that makes sense to me, with his character.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "And how do I look?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "You look terrific.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "And apart from Melanie Griffith's extraordinary hair in that movie, but that was a great -- that was a great comedy role, really, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ":", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "It was.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Melanie Griffith"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Magic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "Is this where you got the love of the business, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "You know, I think I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Do you -- does it diminish what used to be stars on pedestals?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Well, I think fame is the least valuable thing that a successful career gives you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "You know, how could they possibly tell that this is -- that this is something noble, you know, and difficult to achieve?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Your mother was English, I discovered literally seconds before we went on the air, very exciting moment when I discovered it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "It's actually -- 28.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "You're in a business, you know, where divorce come and go like sort of Number 9 buses, how have you managed to avoid that pitfall?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "NN", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Gosh, I don't really know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Or was it honestly more fun being the ne'er-do-well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "It was all kind of crazy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "How the devil are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Do you know, I'm very, very happy today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "I look different in that clip, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "You do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["weekend"]}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "How do you feel now that you're officially a single man again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Well, I think that the -- what happened in the weekend was just an administrative finality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "How is your life in reality at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Well, the limited amount of time I spend in reality I quite enjoy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Have you become, you know, a little less excited about the whole nature of fame and celebrity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Yes, I remember that interview very distinctly, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Is there something society should do to try and put a lid on this before we all go completely mad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "What's the point of it all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "There isn't one, I don't think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Are you an American resident yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Is America refusing to accept you as one of its own then, Russell?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "I love the American people, all of them, every single individual.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Russell"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "How is your temper at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Pretty good, mostly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A.", "Chicago"]}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 538, "question": "What is it, Munchkin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I want to be editor of \"The New Yorker\" and the youngest freelance journalist to be published in \"The New York Times,\" \"L.A. Times\" and \"The Chicago Tribune.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "ORGAN: \"The Wishing Spell,\" why have you written a fairy tale book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "Well, it was a promise that I made to myself when I was 10.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Tell me the narrative?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "Well, the plot is it's about two kids going to the fairy tale world through a magic story book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "How do you deal with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "What do you say to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Well, I don't know if there's anything I could say to them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "And what would you say to yourself as a 14 year old boy now, if you had the chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Well, I think at first, those quotes don't say it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "What do you feel about the way America has moved and the president's endorsement?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Oh, I think that was an amazing endorsement.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Are you standing firmly by your president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I'm 22 and an actor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "You're asking my political advice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "You can vote.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Are you very political?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "I was in high school.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Is it too dangerous to be a young, handsome \"Glee\" star pontificating about politics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "No, I just think it's annoying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "So definitely coming back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Yes, definitely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "ORGAN: You weren't just dropping some terrible bombshell?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "No, no, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "CD", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "You're not going to remove the glee from \"Glee\" for millions of young viewers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "No, maybe a letter or two, but this time -- no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "Are you having a good time with all this or?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "CC", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "I just like progress.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120728pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "And the moral of that is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "You know, don't dilly dally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]